My Christmas Inn is a romance, tv movie film directed by Peter Sullivan.
With the holiday season in full swing, Jen Taylor is about to score a big
promotion at the San Francisco ad agency where she works.
But her life is unexpectedly turned upside down when she
inherits a cozy inn in Alaska from her aunt.
When she goes to inspect the property and meets handsome town attorney Steve
Anderson, she's surprised to find that nothing is what she expected.
The small town community is full of fun and festive Christmas traditions and soon, Jen starts
wondering if the inn might just be the place she belongs, and if Steve could be the Mr.
Right she has been waiting for.
Jen Taylor, played by Tia Mowry.
Susan Taylor, played by Jackée Harry.
Perry Taylor, played by Tim Reid.
Molly Anderson, played by Erin Gray.
Steve Anderson, played by Rob Mayes.
Christmas House Boy, played by Kai Findley.
Snowed-Inn Christmas is a 2017 American-Canadian made-for-television romantic
comedy film directed by Gary Yates, from a screenplay by Carley Smale.
Starring Bethany Joy Lenz and Andrew Walker, it
premiered on 16 December 2017, on Lifetime.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.